so the title of this video might not
make all that much sense but please bear
with me for just one minute
this is gonna be a really valuable video
and it's really gonna help you with how
you're placing your orders whether or
not you're gonna use a market entry on
the bounce when it comes back to the
zone that you're looking for or if
you're just gonna place a blind limit
order and wait for it to come in
[Music]
all right guys what's up my name is
hunter this is hunter FX and if you
haven't seen the channel before I am a
forex Channel quite clearly and I teach
you the absolute best stuff for free and
I do live streaming every Monday to
Friday so you can jump in on that you
can see exactly the trades I'm taking
all that kind of stuff so this video
please it is going to be very valuable
the title doesn't really make all that
much sense but just bear with me here
for a second basically have you ever
wondered would it make more sense for
you to wait to see if there's
confirmation off of a level and then
enter on a smaller timeframe reversal so
zooming into the smaller time frame
waiting for the reversal there and then
entering or do you just place a limit
order and wait until it touches exactly
the point and I'm gonna tell you that
exactly right now whether or not you
should so just quickly tell you exactly
this is what I'm going to tell you you
should do and then I'll show you the
charts so that you can actually see it
in action so first of all you should
place a limit order when there's a
breakout let's say to the upside and
then it's SR flip and it's the first
retest so not the second not the third
the first time it comes back down and
touches it now the reason why I say the
first time is because if it's the second
time well there's one thing that could
happen is first of all the levels
actually weaker so you're probably less
likely to actually be profitable in that
trade but that's irrelevant the
important thing here is that we've now
created a low
and it's gonna be very easy for the
market maker to stop hunt you so if you
do try to put that market that limit
entry and then you put your stop it's
gonna be very obvious where the stops
are so they can stop punch you where you
do not want to place a limit order is
when it's going to be a support support
touch so instead of a support resistance
flip you're just retesting the support
as a support again or resistance as
resistance again so this is a range
based and that is very similar for the
same reason to be very obvious where the
stops are this is gonna be very easy to
stop you out and like I said before you
don't want to do this when it's not the
first test so let's jump into some
examples so I can just show you quickly
what I mean so we're looking at UJ here
on the 15-minute time frame and let me
just show you exactly what I mean here
so we have this consolidation area here
and this is obviously the level that we
need to break out from right so the
first three tests that's right here
that's what I'm telling you
you can place a limit order after it
breaks out on the support resistance
flip with your stop wherever down here
maybe down here it doesn't really matter
where every stop is you could have a
rather tight stop because this is gonna
be the first retest in to be a very
strong level now what I was saying the
second time it comes down you now have
created this low let me just let me just
have better coordination there we go
we've now created this low and it's a
very easy as stopped you out so a lot of
these people they're gonna have their
stops here now and it's gonna be very
easy to stop them out so this level is
also going to be weaker so on the second
retest here we're not gonna want to
place a limit order instead what we're
gonna want to do is wait for it to enter
this zone zoom into the smaller time for
anymore even the 15-minute here wait for
the
trend reversal and then enter long here
with a stop below they're very similar
you get in a little bit later about the
same distance on your stops still gonna
be able to get a good trade and you
don't have to feel like you're left
behind now the thing I was saying about
not wanting to place a limit order
blindly on a retest of a resistance as
resistance or support as support is
simply as this you can see right here
even very clearly let's say that this is
the resistance level you're not gonna
want to place a short here acting as
resistance because first of all you're
not gonna know where to put your stop
there's gonna be a wide stalk and it's
very easy at the exact same idea to stop
you out here so instead what we do is we
wait for price to react to this level we
see it closed within you can zoom in to
a smaller time for a week for that trend
reversal in a smaller time frame and
then enter short with your stop above
there exact same idea we can see this is
a resistance point it breaks up a little
bit then dives back down obviously it
just keeps continuing back up you can
see this pattern absolutely everywhere
on the support side of things this is a
low is a slight sweep there I mean I
could literally choose anywhere on this
chart that's a low sweep break up I can
literally choose anywhere on the chart
and you can see how it is just stupid
to buy random range highs and lows now
you might be saying okay maybe I'll wait
for a deeper retracement so this isn't a
very deep retracement before retesting
lows you might wait for something that
looks like this right and you see that
this is the high there's a deep
retracement and then retest of there you
would want to place a blind limit order
there no exactly same idea same thing
happens slight sweep look at this
happening again slight sweep and then
it's gonna come back down
probably so I've jumped somewhere else
here and I just wanted to make another
point clear on those support support
retest is retests and versus de support
resistance this is kind of another
example where I can show you we would
want to take the retest of the SR flip
right so right here for example this is
the SR flip
you don't want to take the support side
of it here right because this would be
support support and as you can see very
easy will stop you out you can see the
slight weight below let me just show you
the one here even below I I literally
didn't even look for this I just
remembered that I had to add this into
the video I looked at my chart and I saw
this immediately look at that another
one there these are literally everywhere
you look I might be able to find another
one here look at this but I can just
drag this anywhere this is a resistance
side of things you don't want to place
on the resistance side it you'll get
sweep down every single time it's
absolutely unbelievable
so only on the SRS not on the SS or the
RRS back again talking about breakouts
just so you guys can see kind of the
flip side aren't as short here you can
see the price completely breaks down
here this does not count as a retest
because it did not touch it did not
touch it but here you could have placed
a blind short right there and it would
have been very profitable generally
because you know that this first retest
on an SR flip the time and then we can
continue down but but if we look you can
see the second time it breaks up
continues up higher and then eventually
it would stop you out this is much
weaker and we do know where these stops
are now so it's very easy to stop hunt
just slightly higher let me draw a
better line here see there's a slight
stop hunt there because the very obvious
where the stops are gonna be before we
continue back down anyways guys that's
all I have for you today I think that's
actually very simple but I think it's
actually very valuable and I don't think
many people are gonna fall across this
video just because the titles not gonna
make any sense in terms of what I'm
talking about I can't really get the
gist of this along in just a couple
words so if you guys do think that this
is important please make sure you hit
that like button and share it with
whoever because I would like to get that
information along to people I don't
think this is the video the title that
people are gonna think okay that title
sounds interesting and I'm actually
gonna click it but I think it's actually
gonna be valuable for a lot of people
that being said if you guys do like this
content make sure you subscribe make
sure you join the discord so you can
talk and listen to those live streams
when they go live every Monday to Friday
and one more quick bonus tip for anyone
who actually did watch to the end what I
like to do is if I do have a limit order
placed following one of these rules and
it doesn't get filled and it passes the
next level so it goes on and now it's
passed some sort of support or
resistance I will close the limit order
because now I assume that the level is
not quite as strong or it's been
front-run or something like this and
there's gonna be fewer buyers ready to
enter at that time and it's all about
whether or not there's gonna be a lot of
other buyers that contribute to whether
or not I'm gonna place a limit order or
not and then at this point I'm just
gonna wait to see how the market reacts
when it retest that level and then we
might be able to get in it would just be
a slightly worse and
but we can still get a good trade
[Music]